wisepricer.com 2015-04-23

# Privacy Policy - Wiser, The Dynamic Pricing Engine

Wiser's emphasis on your privacy and that of your clients is unmatched and therefore we have established this privacy policy to inform you of your rights. Do keep in mind that as some of Wiser's services are provided by 3rd parties and subcontractors, your personal information is processed and posted over various networks and may be posted upon your request.

## What Personal Information is collected?

Wiser collects some personal information that you provided it, such as your name, email, password, contact information, stores you manage, products geolocation, IP address and other information relating to your account.

Wiser also collects and uses your login credentials in 3rd party services you associate with it, if such credentials are required and no other authentication mechanism is enabled.

## What Non-Personal Information is collected?

Wiser also collects some non-personal information, which may contain information about the products you monitor through Wiser's services competitive information, pricing and other business related information.

## Who has access to your personal information?

Wiser uses the personal information to provide you with services. Apart from Wiser and yourself, no one shall have access to your personal information. Moreover, Wiser's personnel are ordered to refrain from using or accessing your personal information for any reason apart from providing you with support.

## How is your personal information processed?

Wiser processes your personal information both in order to provide you with the Services and in order to create statistical, non-personally identifiable information.

## How can you review your information?

In order to review all the information collected about you through the Services, you may open your settings dashboard in the Wiser website.

## How can you delete your information?

You may specifically request to delete your account, as well as all other personal information, by sending an email to info@wiser.com
